{
    "id": "b8bcdb3d1bb64b568b54ef38a5c77011",
    "title": "English Vocabulary Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "An …………………… play like that won’t last two weeks.",
            "description": "Insipid means boring.",
            "answers": [
                "insipid",
                "spunky",
                "sophisticated"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e63d81077f924f11962d41170047db0f"
        },
        {
            "question": "The ……………………….. child needs discipline.",
            "description": "Insolent means disrespectful.",
            "answers": [
                "deferential",
                "submissive",
                "insolent"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "24c674ba67094d9598b11627b4504a7f"
        },
        {
            "question": "The article ……………………….. that the officer was bribed.",
            "description": "To insinuate is to imply. ",
            "answers": [
                "protracted",
                "insinuated",
                "deliberated"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "79ba1637d24140299e8e9b71823f99ae"
        },
        {
            "question": "The flying saucer sighting was ………………………….",
            "description": "Inexplicable means mysterious.",
            "answers": [
                "fathomable",
                "explicable",
                "inexplicable"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0528d139646a4aef8d3ef1ae9a7f021a"
        },
        {
            "question": "He would have preferred anger to her cold …………………………",
            "description": "Indifference means lack of concern.",
            "answers": [
                "difference",
                "deference",
                "indifference"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b78468a317544d39b529596fb93b4bd6"
        },
        {
            "question": "Many ……………………… people receive government aid.",
            "description": "Indigent means poor. ",
            "answers": [
                "indigenous",
                "ingenious",
                "indigent"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "42cc08d92cc24a8e9bd082e689d133df"
        },
        {
            "question": "Reports of child abuse aroused public …………………………..",
            "description": "Indignation means fury.",
            "answers": [
                "indignation",
                "complacency",
                "discrimination"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fc2ca27d8be24b24b4e5fe5b7de5bcad"
        },
        {
            "question": "The innocent child gave a …………………….. answer to the question.",
            "description": "Guileless means honest or open.",
            "answers": [
                "crafty",
                "artful",
                "guileless"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c0521486553b49cfbab120e8a7b114fe"
        },
        {
            "question": "That was a ………………………….. abuse of his authority.",
            "description": "Flagrant means shockingly bad.",
            "answers": [
                "flagrant",
                "fierce",
                "fragrant"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "baa4d7f68f7445a0a539f2f4669bf6de"
        },
        {
            "question": "The company has ……………………….. tremendous losses.",
            "description": "Endured means suffered.",
            "answers": [
                "endured",
                "recovered",
                "cleared"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "34e86aa0e9fa46669e0fe402cf6c0bbd"
        },
        {
            "question": "We should all ………………………… to be more considerate of others.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "inspire",
                "proscribe",
                "endeavor"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "fb43c55335f6448896c71eb7de10a912"
        },
        {
            "question": "The sorcerer ……………………….. the beautiful princess.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "emulated",
                "enchanted",
                "enthralled"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "04f7467ac8204b42857e0e085900ffb1"
        }
    ]
}